(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
TAKANASHI KIARA'S
END OF THE YEAR
3D CELEBRATION
10... 9... 8... 7... 6...
5... 4... 3... 2... 1... 0
Takanashi Kiara's
END OF THE YEAR
3D CELEBRATION
LIVE START!
Around the world, everyone says
That love is just like a dream
Feel like I'm melting from the heat
Love it, it feels so surreal
Oh yeah
Ooh, just like that, you know just how it goes
Don't ever stop
...already know.
You're just so sweet, my favorite.
Got me wanting more, so tasty, yeah.
I ain't got no worries.
I feel good, good, good.
The warm sun on me.
I wanna go and party.
Don't let this love end.
No, I won't pretend.
My best recipe for love is you plus me.
I wanna try it now.
Try it now!
Hey!
I'm going one, two, one, two, three.
It tastes so, so, so sweet.
When you go and kiss me.
I'm taking that perfect picture.
You stuck to me like a sticker.
I'm going one, two, one, two, three.
It tastes so, so, so sweet.
Go that way.
I-ye-ye-ye, I-ye-ye-ye.
Keep going, you know me.
Hey!
I'm way too beat to be naively sweet.
So sweet, it's hypnotizing.
Got you dancing to my beat.
You can be my boo.
Can you see me, see me?
Babe, I need you gimme, gimme.
No more hesitation, don't think twice.
'Cause you're mine.
The warm sun on me.
I wanna go and party.
Don't let this love end.
No, I won't pretend.
My best recipe for love is you plus me.
I wanna try it now.
Try it now!
Hey!
I'm going one, two, one, two, three.
It tastes so, so, so sweet.
When you go and kiss me.
I'm taking that perfect picture.
You stuck to me like a sticker.
I'm going one, two, one, two, three.
It tastes so, so, so sweet.
Go that way.
I-ye-ye-ye, I-ye-ye-ye.
Keep going, you know me.
Pineapple!
Hey!
Pineapple, pineapple, pin-ya.
Come on boys, let's go!
Come on baby, do it over, over.
Hold my hand and let's fly.
And let's take it to...
...the sky!
I'm going one, two, one, two, three.
It tastes so, so, so sweet.
When you go and kiss me.
I'm taking that perfect picture.
You stuck to me like a sticker.
I'm going one, two, one, two, three.
It tastes so, so, so sweet.
Go that way.
I-ye-ye-ye, I-ye-ye-ye.
Keep going, you know me.
Pineapple!
Hey!
Waking up in shades of blue.
VOICE
Lyrics • Composition: KIRA
I don't know where I am or how I got to you.
Try to reach out but I can't move.
I'm like a broken instrument, so out of tune.
Why won't they listen to me anyway?
I wanna be and I'm not gonna say I'm sorry.
Just so you let me stay, no.
Whatever you think of me, leave it alone.
I don't wanna live in the shade of her throne.
I keep hearing pieces of a melody playing in my head.
Fragments of a past that won't let me forget.
Someone that I used to be hanging on the edge...
...of a blurry silhouette. I wonder...
...when you look at me who do you remember?
Broken memories tied us together.
Tell me honestly do you recognize my voice?
Voice.
Thin air, so hard to breathe.
The wall that I'm facing is just too cold and too lonely.
Wish that I still could feel, still could feel the things...
...that back then I used to feel.
Oh, and all I ever wanted was to be accepted by you.
Wish that you and I still laughed and that's only my wish.
Why won't you listen to me anyway?
I'm gonna be and I'm not gonna say I'm sorry.
Just to stay, stay.
Whatever you think of me, leave it alone.
I don't wanna live in the shade of her throne, oh.
I keep hearing pieces of a melody playing in my head.
Fragments of a past that won't let me forget.
Someone that I used to be hanging on the edge...
...of a blurry silhouette.
The blurry silhouette...
...I wonder...
...when you look at me, who do you remember?
Broken memories, time we spent together
Tell me honestly, do you recognize...
...my voice? Voice?
It looks so odd to me...
...the picture you paint of us
I don't need to remember
Let me be, take me just as I am as...
...everything disappears
I shout to heaven's seven!
Let me be, take me just as I am, yeah
I keep praying
Fragments of a melody playing in my head
Fragments of a past that they won't let me forget
I'm more than I used to be hanging on the edge...
...of the blurry silhouette I wonder...
...when you look at me, who do you remember?
Broken memories, time we spent together
Tell me honestly, do you think that I could ever...
...find a voice to call my own?
Voice! Voice!
ロボキッス / 唄 / 小鳥遊キアラ 夏色まつり
RoboKiss / Sung by Takanashi Kiara & Natsuiro Matsuri
Lyrics / Composition: つんく
Lyrics / Composition: Tsunku
お熱い仲とはここのこと
The two of us are so hot together
可愛いいあいつは分け前さ
That cute person is my share
誰も彼もが平凡だダメダメ
Everyone else is so ordinary, no good
どこに投げたの運の目
Where did you throw the lucky dice?
デートの誘い合言葉
The password for a date invitation
穴が開いてる伝説まだまだ
The legend still has holes in it
恋くらい
At least some love
させてよ当然
Let me have it, of course
スキスキスキスキをください
Please give me like-like-like-like
スキスキスキスキは無限大
Like-like-like-like is infinite
スキスキスキスキはわかるわ
I understand like-like-like-like
スキスキスキスキロボどなたさま
Like-like-like-like, who are you Mr. Robot?
シャバラララララ...
Shaba rara rara rara...
ロボロボ
Robo-robo
これでアイツとは友情
With this, it's friendship with him
それじゃ彼氏と不平等
Then it's unequal with a boyfriend
なんて理屈なの勉強ダメダメ
What kind of logic is that? Studying is no good
計算ずくでもあたふた
Even if it's calculated, I'm flustered
誰も承知でへっちゃら
Everyone knows and doesn't care
恋の行方はありがたいただけ
The destination of love is just gratefully accepted
いつまでも
Forever
子供じゃないのね
We're not children anymore
スキスキスキスキをください
Please give me like-like-like-like
スキスキスキスキは故障中
Like-like-like-like is out of order
スキスキスキスキはひとりじゃ
Like-like-like-like can't be done alone
スキスキスキスキだれもできません
Like-like-like-like, nobody can do it [alone]
ロボキッス
Robot Kiss
…は　できませ～ん
...I can't do it!
シャバラララララララ～
Shabaralalaralala
ロボボッ
Robobo
キッス！
Kiss!
せーの
One, two!
でもそんなんじゃだめ
But that's no good
もうそんなんじゃほら
Look, already like that
心は進化するよ　もっともっと
The heart will evolve, more and more
恋愛サーキュレーション
Ren'ai Circulation
言葉にすれば消えちゃう関係なら　言葉を消せばいいやって思ってた
If it's a relationship that vanishes when put into words, I thought it'd be better to just erase the words
恐れてた　だけどあれ？なんか違うかも
I was afraid, but wait? Something might be different
千里の道も一歩から　石のように固いそんな意志で
A journey of a thousand miles starts with a single step, with a will as hard as a stone
塵も積もれば大和撫子？　「し」抜きで　いや「し」抜きで
Even dust when piled up becomes a Yamato Nadeshiko? Without the "shi"... no, without the "shi"!
ふわふわり　ふわふわる　あなたが名前を呼ぶ
Softly floating, lightly drifting, you call my name
それだけで宙へ浮かぶ
Just that makes me float into space
ふわふわる　ふわふわり　あなたが笑っている
Lightly drifting, softly floating, you are smiling
それだけで笑顔になる
Just that makes me smile
神様ありがとう　運命のいたずらでも
Thank you, God, even if it's a prank of fate
めぐり逢えたことが　しあわせなの
The fact that we could meet makes me happy
でもそんなんじゃだめ
But that's no good
もうそんなんじゃほら
Look, already like that
心は進化するよ　もっともっと
The heart will evolve, more and more
そうそんなんじゃやだ
Yes, I don't want it like that
ねぇそんなんじゃまだ
Hey, it's not enough like that
私のこと見ててね　ずっとずっと
Please keep watching me, forever and ever
私の中のあなたほど　あなたの中の私の存在はまだまだ
As much as you are within me, my presence within you is still far from it
大きくないこともわかってるけれど
I know it's not that big yet
今この同じ瞬間　共有してる時間
Right now, this same moment, the time we are sharing
塵も積もれば大和撫子？　略してちりつもやまとなでこ！
Even dust when piled up becomes a Yamato Nadeshiko? In short, Chiritsumo Yamato Nadeko!
くらくらり　くらくらる　あなたを見上げたら
Dizzy, spinning, when I look up at you
それだけで眩しすぎて
Just that is too dazzling
くらくらる　くらくらり　あなたを想っている
Spinning, dizzy, I am thinking of you
それだけでとけてしまう
Just that makes me melt away
神様ありがとう　運命のいたずらでも
Thank you, God, even if it's a prank of fate
めぐり逢えたことが　しあわせなの
The fact that we could meet makes me happy
恋する季節は　欲張りサーキュレーション
The season of love is a greedy circulation
恋する気持ちは　欲張りサーキュレーション
The feeling of love is a greedy circulation
恋する瞳は　欲張りサーキュレーション
The eyes in love are a greedy circulation
恋する乙女は　欲張りサーキュレーション
A maiden in love is a greedy circulation
ふわふわり　ふわふわる　あなたが名前を呼ぶ
Softly floating, lightly drifting, you call my name
それだけで宙へ浮かぶ
Just that makes me float into space
ふわふわる　ふわふわり　あなたが笑っている
Lightly drifting, softly floating, you are smiling
それだけで笑顔になる
Just that makes me smile
神様ありがとう　運命のいたずらでも
Thank you, God, even if it's a prank of fate
めぐり逢えたことが　しあわせなの
The fact that we could meet makes me happy
でもそんなんじゃだめ
But that's no good
もうそんなんじゃほら
Look, already like that
心は進化するよ　もっともっと
The heart will evolve, more and more
そうそんなんじゃやだ
Yes, I don't want it like that
ねぇそんなんじゃまだ
Hey, it's not enough like that
私のこと見ててね　ずっとずっと
Please keep watching me, forever and ever
Kikkeriki! Hello!
Say hello to Aki-senpai!
アロナ！アキロゼんたーるです！
Alona! I'm Aki Rosenthal!
We danced Renai Circulation together.
But before that, we danced with Matsuri-senpai, right?
So let's get Matsuri-senpai!
元気に！お…ちょっと服が違うけどね。
Energetically! Oh... the outfit is a bit different though.
あ、そんなに小さくないけど…
Ah, I'm not that small but...
お姉さん組。
The big sister group.
あとうちの子ども？
And our child?
バブー！
Babu!
やめなさい。すぐママにされちゃうから。
Stop it. You'll make me a mom immediately.
I want to ask a question.
質問したい！
I want to ask a question!
お二人は今年一番嬉しかったこと…
For you two, what was the thing you were most happy about...
What was the thing you were most happy about this year?
アキゼは、大好きなクレープ屋さんのコラボもいっぱいできたし…
For me, I got to do many collaborations with my favorite crepe shop...
案件も来たこと！
...and getting projects!
待って、クレープうまいし、美味しい。
Wait, crepes are good and delicious.
二人も来てくれたしね。
You two also came, right?
ね！美味しかった！またご馳走してください。
Right! It was delicious! Please treat us again.
もちろん近だよ。お腹すいた。いいよ、いつでも食べにおいで。
Of course. I'm hungry. Sure, come eat anytime.
まつりはやっぱり今年もリスナーさんと楽しいひと時を過ごせたことかにゃ。
For me, it was being able to spend a fun time with the listeners this year too.
Her favorite thing was just being with the viewers...
...and hers was, you know, being a crepe maker, which was really good, yeah.
私はホロサマーのテーマ曲に参加したことと…
For me, it was participating in the Hololive Summer theme song and...
あと三年目にしてやっと3Dお披露目できたこと！っていう。
...finally having my 3D debut in my third year!
It's almost 2024.
もうすぐ2024年。
来年、私とやりたいこと！
Next year, things you want to do with me!
What do you want to do with me next year?
せっかく三人今いますから、ま、アキゼの家に行ってご飯食べたい。
Since the three of us are here, I want to go to Aki-ze's house and eat.
それこそね、ほらダンスできるから、ダンスもね、一緒にやりたい。
Exactly, we can dance, so I want to dance together too.
ゲームもしたい。と英語も教えてほしい。
I want to play games too. And I want you to teach me English.
二人に英語教えられる英語メンバーはいっぱいいますから…
There are many English members who can teach you two English...
私はドイツ語教えてあげる！
...so I'll teach you German!
Guten Morgenってドイツ語？
Is 'Guten Morgen' German?
そうそうそう！おはようございます。
Yes, yes, yes! It means good morning.
So maybe we'll, you know, we'll get some cooking collabs next year...
...maybe some dancing, and maybe I'll teach them German, who knows.
But yeah, with that, let's move on to the next section!
ということで、次のアレに行きましょう。
So, let's move on to the next section.
ありがとう！バブー！バイバイ！
Thank you! Babu! Bye-bye!
始めようぜ
Let's get started
ぶちかませて
Give it your all
夢見てるんじゃね
Don't just dream
上がってこぜ
Let's rise up
雑草みたいな俺たちの生き様を
Our way of life, like weeds
雑草のうた
Lyrics: 岩里祐穂 Composition: 井上慎二郎
Weed's Song
Lyrics: Yuho Iwasato Composition: Shinjiro Inoue
笑いたい奴がいたら笑えばいい
If there's someone who wants to laugh, let them laugh
同じことなんてしたくない
I don't want to do the same things
人と同じである意味信じない
I don't believe in the meaning of being the same as others
だって皆違うのに
Because everyone is different
何度でも生まれてやるんだ
I'll be reborn as many times as it takes
何度でも格好つけないままでいいじゃん
It's fine to stay uncool as many times as it takes
未完成で死ぬまでカンカン
Unfinished and blazing until death
誰でも土砂降り雨でも
Anyone, even in a downpour
吹雪の夜でも
Even on a blizzard night
倒れたって起き上がれる
Even if I fall, I can get back up
踏まれて 踏まれて 踏まれて
Being stepped on, stepped on, stepped on
もっと強くなるんだ
I will become even stronger
Keep your head up
甘えてんじゃねぇ
Don't be soft
始めようぜ
Let's get started
ぶちかませて
Give it your all
夢見てるんじゃね
Don't just dream
雑草のうた
Weed Song
名前を持たない 道端の草みたいに
Like a weed on the roadside without a name
誰にも知られていない気分はどうだい
How does it feel to be known by no one?
言い訳してる暇はない
There's no time for making excuses
落ち込んでるそんな場合じゃない
This is no time to be feeling down
そうさ時代は変わるよ
That's right, the times are changing
生きてるだけで
Just being alive
奇跡だって
Is a miracle
俺たち
We are...
ボロボロになったっていいじゃん
It's okay if we're worn to tatters
ゴールドなんて
Things like gold
まだまだ石ころ
Are still just pebbles
道でも 線路の脇でも
On the road, or by the railroad tracks
歩道の端でも
Or even at the edge of the sidewalk
根っ子生やしてやればいい
All we need to do is take root
蹴られて 蹴られて 蹴られて
Kicked, kicked, kicked
何か見つけ出すんだ
We'll find something
You can do it
諦めんじゃねえ
Don't you give up
夢見て 夢見て
Dreaming, dreaming
笑って 笑って
Laughing, laughing
悩んで 悩んで
Worrying, worrying
涙流してもいいんだ
It's okay to shed tears
夢中で 夢中で
Obsessed, obsessed
不安で 不安で
Anxious, anxious
叫んで 叫んで
Screaming, screaming
求め続けてやろうぜ
Let's keep on searching
カンカン照りでも
Even under a blazing sun
土砂降り雨でも
Or in a downpour of rain
吹雪の夜でも
Even on a blizzard night
倒れたって起き上がれる
Even if we fall, we can get back up
踏まれて 踏まれて 踏まれて
Stepped on, stepped on, stepped on
もっと強くなるんだ
We'll become even stronger
Keep your head up
甘えてんじゃねえ
Don't be so soft
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey!
ぶちかませ
Let 'em have it
夢見てんじゃねえ
Don't just keep dreaming
あがいて行こうぜ
Let's keep struggling on
ピース
Peace
It’s the birds-eye-view, and the pressure is crazy
Fire N Ice
Lyrics: Mori Calliope / TeddyLoid / Composition: TeddyLoid
You better step up, drop, roll, and knock off the sweat at the door
Flights like that kind of fire
The Phoenix rises higher
Frigid, frozen, no limits, the cold
Tremble low, tremble low
支配したいの 君の心を
I want to dominate your heart
行こう 望むまま
Let's go, just as you wish
Fired up, fired up now / Hot passion never back down
Freeze up, freeze up now / Not about to vent to you
Fire N Ice, step light now / High pressure, turn it up now
Fire N Ice, fire ice now / This world’s all smoke and mirrors
君の思惑
Your expectations
超えて超えて
Surpass them, surpass them
知りたい気持ちなんだ
It's a feeling of wanting to know
冷めた醒めた
Chilled, awakened
Blazing, unchanging, no safe thing about this heat
Witness me, hit the speed, transcribe script
Feeling’s got me freezing now
執着させてよ
Let me get attached
体中今 駆け巡らせば
If it surges through my whole body now
Control, overflow
掴まえたいの 君の心を
I want to catch your heart
でもね だって
But you see, because...
Fired up, fired up now / Hot passion never back down
Freeze up, freeze up now / Not about to vent to you
Fire N Ice, step light now / High pressure, turn it up now
Fire N Ice, fire ice now / This world’s all smoke and mirrors
煩いその口
That noisy mouth of yours
閉じて閉じて
Close it, close it
許せないの今は
I can't forgive it right now
止めて止めて
Stop it, stop it
Caught up in the eye of a storm of flames / It’s not complicated but a nuanced game
Pass you once again give you something I can’t shake / The chance to know somebody who takes moves to make
So what you waiting for you gotta burn it up / Because when it rains it pours you gotta earn the love
Giving me next and never get enough
Cause you and I are spies above, you got it?
Fire it up, fire it up now
High pressure never back down
Freeze it out, freeze it out now
Not about to bend to you
Fire and ice death and life now
High pressure turn it up loud
Fire and ice fire and ice now
This world's a smoke and mirror
君の思うがままに
Exactly as you wish
超えて超えて
Crossing over, crossing over
ちょっと息を止めて
Hold your breath for a moment
寒さの中で
Within the cold
Thank you everybody!
Whoa! Hype hype hype hype hype!
TakaMori! TakaMori!
Thank you so much everybody!
How was it? How was it? Do you like it?
I hope so. We worked very hard on that.
That's our brand new song!
Our brand new song! But since we wanted
to talk more about it...
...we're gonna get down closer to you guys
so you can hear us, right?
That's right. You guys can hear us properly?
Hello! We're gonna jump, right?
Yes, are you ready to jump? It's pretty far.
Wait, are you sure? Okay... let's go!
Kiara, okay! AHH!
Swag! Hey! Hey!
Easy, so easy. Easy. Such a high jump up there.
I can't believe we didn't die.
Must be because of me.
That's crazy. Oh man, nice!
You guys hear us and see us better now?
Hello, hello! Hi! Loud and clear. TakaMori!
TakaMori! TakaMori! Welcome, welcome, welcome!
I hope you guys enjoyed the song.
I think it was hype. I think so too. It was hype.
It's a banger. It's a banger. It's a banger.
So now we can talk about the song,
and I think you know the most details about it.
So give me the deets!
Well, this song has been in the works
for about two years.
A long time. Hey, everyone's really
busy in Holo, right?
But you know what?
It was finally time to finish it.
Yeah, cause I said, "Calli, I'm doing
this birthday live thing..."
"...do you maybe want to release it in time
for that?" And that kind of got us rolling.
Finally got the ball rolling, got it moving.
And um, it's called "Fire N Ice".
Which I couldn't... Are you fire? No. Am I fire?
Is that a real question? She's messing
with me. She knows.
I'm the fire! And you're the ice! Oh god.
The song is about us, and that we're very different...
...but when we get together, we make magic happen.
Bangers, etc.
Yeah, that was the basic idea.
And it's produced by TeddyLoid...
...who always makes bangers. TeddyLoid
always makes bangers. So thank you.
Arigatou gozaimasu. Lyrics by both
myself and TeddyLoid.
So I hope you guys enjoy it. The music
video is on my channel.
It came out like a couple days ago,
so go check it out.
It's so cool. And the music video is really
neat. It's by Kanaru.
Kanaru who also always only makes bangers.
So be sure you check it.
Should we show them the jacket?
The jacket? Oh, yeah, the jacket. Check it out.
You guys, jacket? We're selling a jacket?
Oh my god, she's messing with me again.
Check it out, ta-da! There it is.
We're a meme right now. Hold on, ja-jaan!
Oh, it's super nice.
Who drew the jacket? It was by Gumshue.
Thank you so much, Gumshue.
Wow, wow, kamsahamnida. Oh, okay.
We're running out of time, but I also want to say...
Wow, wow, thank you. Oh, okay.
...we came from, you know, small TakaMori
doing like little cover like "Wowa World"...
...and now we have original song. Thank you,
Calli, for organizing it. Yeah, no problem.
Dankeschön. And yeah, look at us being cute.
Wow, we look nice together. Pose!
恥ずかしい。 It's so embarrassing.
This is embarrassing. It's so embarrassing.
Wait, thank you for supporting TakaMori.
I guess we look cute, maybe? Very cute.
Dankeschön. All right, Calli, thanks for having me.
Thank you for coming and dancing with me.
It was so fun! Thank you! I'm getting
kicked out again.
Yes, sorry. I figured as much. Bye bye!
See you soon. Oh well, good luck! Enjoy
everybody! Bye bye!
Peace!
And with that, I still have a lot more songs for you guys.
まだまだいっぱいありますよ！
There's still plenty more!
You're gonna like this next one, I think.
I'm pretty sure.
Enjoy.
粛聖！！ロリ神レクイエム☆
Shukusei!! Loli Kami Requiem☆
Lyrics: まろん Composition: D.watt
Lyrics: Maron Composition: D.watt
鐘を鳴らせばこの通り
As the bell rings out like this
これは救済のレクイエム
This is a requiem for salvation
せーの！
Ready, go!
ざばざば最高！
Zaba-zaba, the best!
かぷかぷ天国！
Kapu-kapu, heaven!
1 2 3 4!
ごめんなさいが聞こえない
I can't hear any apologies
粛聖！！ロリ神レクイエム☆
Shukusei!! Loli Kami Requiem☆
神にすがるな
Don't cling to God.
泥水で口を洗え
Wash your mouth with muddy water.
法廷で会おう
I'll see you in court.
さあ おまわりさん
Now, Mr. Policeman,
連れて行って
take them away.
妄想しか取り柄のない
You pathetic person
可哀想な人
with nothing but delusions.
おいちゃん おいちゃん
Mister, mister...
その姿を世に見せられますか？
Can you show that side of you to the world?
おいちゃん おいちゃん かわいいよ
Mister, mister, you're cute!
わあ ありがとう お疲れ様です
Wow, thank you! Good work!
ロリ ロリ 神降臨
Loli, loli, the God descends!
まぎらわしい奴らに用心
Beware of those suspicious guys.
ハートもうぶなら
If your heart is still innocent,
早く消えてください
please get out of here quickly.
ロリ ロリ ロリ 神降臨
Loli, loli, loli, the God descends!
鐘を鳴らせばこの通り
Ring the bell and here she is.
とても優しくて 素敵な お兄さん
Such a very kind and wonderful mister.
ラブ注入 ほら ねえねえ 死な...
Injecting love. Hey, hey, die...
ほら 世の中には こんなに気持ち悪い人たちが
Look, there are so many creepy people
蔓延っているんです
infesting this world.
みんな ぶち上げますよ！ せい！
Everyone, let's fire it up! Sei!
さあさあ 獄中へ Go back to the 刑務所
Now, now, to prison! Go back to the jail!
1, 2, 3, 4 ごめんなさい？
1, 2, 3, 4. "I'm sorry"?
は？ ごめんなさいが聞こえない
Huh? I can't hear your apology.
粛聖!! ロリ神レクイエム☆
Holy Purge!! Loli God Requiem☆
はい ここにいる皆さん 気持ちお耳づくのお時間です
Alright everyone here, it's time to treat your creepy ears.
その腐りきった耳を ゴリゴリゴリゴリ...
Grinding and grinding those rotten ears...
よく聞いてくださいね
Listen very carefully, okay?
さっさ 刺そう キモ キモ
Hurry up and stab, gross, gross.
うるさい 黙ってもらっていいですか？
Shut up. Could you please be quiet?
嫌いです かわいそう
I hate you. How pathetic.
ダサ 弱 見っともない
Lame, weak, shameful.
常識も何もない お兄さん お姉さん
Misters and misses with no common sense,
救いようもないゴミだね お前ら
you're all hopeless trash.
汚物消毒 救済版
Sanitizing the filth, Salvation Edition.
固有結界 発動
Reality Marble: Activation.
粛聖!! ういビーム!!
Holy Purge!! Ui-beam!!
今 すべてを 許します
I forgive everything now.
この世の醜さを
The ugliness of this world,
集めて描いてみるよ
I'll gather it and try to draw it.
真っ白なキャンバスが
The pure white canvas
汚れて泣いている
is stained and crying.
ロリ 振り向いた少女は
Loli, the girl who looked back
そっと 手を掴む
softly grabs my hand.
楽園などないから
Since there is no such thing as paradise.
大きなお友達のみんな
All my "big friends,"
お前らが落ち込んでいる今日明日に
what meaning is there in your depressed
何の意味があるの？
today and tomorrow?
ねぇ 死んでよ
Hey, just die.
ういビームの加減がわかんないんだ
I don't know how to hold back my Ui-beam.
ロリ ロリ 神降臨
Loli, loli, the God descends!
さよなら 笑顔でバイバイ
Goodbye, bye-bye with a smile.
非道を どうぞ
Please, take this inhumanity.
この手で堕ちてあげゆ
I'll let you fall by my hand.
ロリ ロリ 神降臨
Loli, loli, the God descends!
鐘を鳴らせばこの通り
Ring the bell and here she is.
とても優しくて 素敵な お兄さん
Such a very kind and wonderful mister.
楽園で ほら
Look, in paradise...
ねえねえ 死な
Hey, hey, die.
それは 救世の
It's a requiem
レクイエム
of salvation.
せーの！
Ready, go!
さあさあ 獄中へ Go back to the 刑務所
Now, now, to prison! Go back to the jail!
1, 2, 3, 4 ごめんなさい？
1, 2, 3, 4. "I'm sorry"?
は？ ごめんなさいが聞こえない
Huh? I can't hear your apology.
粛聖!! ロリ神レクイエム☆
Holy Purge!! Loli God Requiem☆
本当に 気持ち悪い
You're really creepy.
Passing by familiar roads
I couldn't find the reason why
The Great Wanderer
Who I am you couldn't know
Stuck in the ruins of my delusion
In between the two realities
My own desire keeps me higher
...to you
Ooh...
Moving faster than the light can
I'm in the absence
Alone looking back
Did I lose my way?
I can't see the day
When I can reach you again
And then I let go
I can hear your voice
Leading me through the void
Fade away
Through the gray
Eternally I'm walking by
The lands of push before my eyes alone
The silence deafening
Still reaching out to you
Connections lost, the vice of light
It turns to dust, so I'll survive one day
Eventually the light
It will lead me back to you see me
Faith is gone, the well is drying
No more believing
Just deceiving
Ooh...
Feel the daylight on the edge of pulse
I can't feel the beat
Fall back into sleep
Did I lose my way?
I can't see the day
When I can reach you again
And then I let go
I can hear your voice
Leading me through the void
Fade away
Through the gray
Eternally I'm walking by
The lands of push before my eyes alone
The silence deafening
Still reaching out to you
Connections lost, the vice of light
It turns to dust, so I'll survive one day
Eventually the light
It will lead me back to you see me
That was TGW, "The Great Wanderer"!
You were all waiting for that one, weren't you? Me too, me too!
Ah, I feel like the vibe was definitely there. Did you feel it? Ah...
"The Great Wanderer" on my album, Point of View right now! So if you want to hear more of that...
If that was the first time you heard it, then what are you doing?
Go listen to my album, please!
Yeah, I really like the choreo, so I hope I can dance to it again sometime soon.
And actually, I don't know if you know it yet...
But right after this—because this is, you know, as you can see, already ending soon...
もうすぐ終わるんですけど...
It's ending soon, but...
実はこのあとメン限あります！
Actually, there's a members-only part after this!
There is a members-only part following right after this!
So please check it out. It's the first time I get to do something like that.
So it's really exciting for me.
My members, I hope you will enjoy what I have prepared for you.
Just a little bit, you know, just a little bit extra.
Yeah, and besides that, of course, I just mentioned I want to, you know, talk about my album...
Because originally I wanted to do this live during the time when the album was released...
But didn't quite work out. So let me say it now, guys!
私のアルバムから、いくつもね、今日、新曲を披露させていただきましたけども、
I performed several new songs from my album today, but...
聴いてますか？
Are you listening to them?
Point of View on Spotify, on Amazon Music, on Apple Music...
Everywhere! Please listen to Point of View!
Hi! And, yeah, besides that...
Thank you guys so much for waiting for this.
I'm so happy that today is finally the day that I can show off some of my new songs...
...some of my old songs and have some great guests over.
Yeah, did you enjoy everything?
What was your favorite performance? What was your favorite guest? Hm? Hm? Hm?
Me too! Oh, what a coincidence!
Mm, yes. Uh, well, besides this...
This stream is End Of The Year Concert...
...so I want to say...
Hello everybody.
2023 was a blast.
Thank you for supporting me,
thank you for supporting Hololive English and Hololive as a whole.
And me as a musician, of course,
this year was all about that.
Me creating my album and, yeah, more musical activities.
So let's see where the new year, the new year 2024 will lead us to.
Hopefully more music.
And you guys are gonna join me, right?
Mm!
はい、2023年も終わりなので、今年ありがとうございましたというのもね、
Yes, 2023 is ending, so I also wanted to say
言いたかったです。
thank you for this year.
ありがとうございました、皆さん。
Thank you, everyone.
And the last song, next song is the last song. It's also from my album.
次の曲がラストの曲なんですけど、
The next song is the last song,
そちらも私のアルバムの曲であって...
and that one is also a song from my album...
It actually didn't get a 3D MV,
so I want you guys to look closely at the performance and at the choreography, okay?
Alright!
Then please listen to: Sleep Talking.
Sleep Talking
Lyrics: monii / Johnny R  Composition: monii / Johnny R / WD / KIRA / ADILE
It's been a long day.
Will you call me?
Yeah, you've got me sleep talking...
Sleep talking...
Oh, where did you go?
Talk to me, boy.
I'm up late already, hit midnight.
(Ooh, baby)
Convince myself I'm doing alright, but you know...
Taking one step,
taking one back.
When you text me saying "No way".
Not fair, not fair, not fair.
Your eyes they telling me come here now I can't wait.
Your body got me talking,
breathless as you got me wanting.
Oh baby don't you know,
got me I'm hooked I go.
I'm breathing you in I just can't forget,
boy you got me stressed I'm just wanting it.
Oh baby it's what you do.
You got me sleep talking in my dreams I'm sleep talking
all these nights it's you.
No more hiding it, na-na,
caught up in your bed sleep talking
in my dreams I'm sleep talking
all these nights it's you.
(Sleep, sleep, sleep talking)
Hey mister, you got me,
all day I'm sleeping.
I'm breathing your voice, I ain't got a choice,
yeah just like that baby you might never know.
Hey don't you leave me alone,
I'm waiting here on the phone.
So baby just gonna make a call and I'll know
if you really are in it, give it to me now boy.
Your body got me talking,
breathless as you got me wanting.
Oh baby don't you know,
got me I'm hooked I go.
I'm breathing you in I just can't forget,
boy you got me stressed I'm just wanting it.
Oh baby it's what you do.
You got me sleep talking in my dreams I'm sleep talking
all these nights it's you.
No more hiding it, na-na,
caught up in your bed sleep talking
in my dreams I'm sleep talking
all these nights it's you.
(Sleep, sleep, sleep talking)
Sleep talking in the night yes sleep talking
oh that's right yeah.
Bambela bamba bambelo, you got me feeling so right.
Sleep talking in the night yes sleep talking
oh that's right yeah.
Bambela bamba bambelo, you got me sleep talking day.
Hello?
Baby who am I talking to?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you want it baby you know just what you gotta do.
You know you want it,
just one look and so don't pretend. Whoo!
Hello?
Baby who are you talking to?
Ooh, it's the moment I can't escape.
I'm breathless I,
I can't deny.
Oh, it's you who made me this way!
Sleep talking in my dreams I'm sleep talking
all these nights it's you.
No more hiding it, na-na,
caught up in your bed sleep talking
in my dreams I'm sleep talking
all these nights it's you.
(Sleep, sleep, sleep talking)
Sleep talking in the night yes sleep talking
oh that's right yeah.
Bambela bamba bambelo, you got me feeling so right.
Sleep talking in the night yes sleep talking
oh that's right yeah.
Bambela bamba bambelo, you got me sleep talking day.
ちょっと最初の方流してほしい。
I want you to play the beginning for a bit.
Yeah, yeah. Beat, beat.
いっくよー！
Here we go!
よいしょー！
Yoisho!
落ちないでねー！
Don't fall off, okay?!
Try now, go!
えー、ありがとう！
Aw, thank you!
OK, yeah!
お疲れ様！
Good job!
お疲れ、ありがとう！
Good job, thank you!
あ、いい、いい、いい。
Ah, nice, nice, nice.
うおー。
Whoa.
お、でっか。
Oh, they're huge.
TAKANASHI KIARA'S end of the Year 3D CELEBRATION
Rising to the peak
See me, see me
Give me, give me
Think twice, 'cause you're
Moving on and make me wanna go and party
No no, no no
Love is always in the way
Try now, go!
Wake up that right attitude